Guide to the Honey Lee Cottrell papers, 1950-2015.
Cottrell, Honey Lee papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Honey Lee Cottrell papers, 1950-2015.
7822
Cottrell, Honey Lee,
4.1 cubic feet and digital recordings.
Photographs, artwork, and printed materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Personal papers and photographic archives.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Honey Lee Cottrell was a noted photographer who helped define lesbian erotica in the 1980s through her contributions to the women's sex magazine On Our Backs. She studied at the National Sex Forum and was a volunteer switchboard operator at San Francisco Sex Information. Her photographs appeared in I Am My Lover (1979), Coming to Power (1981), A Dyke's Bike Repair Handbook (1990), and Nothing But the Girl (1996), as well as in magazines including The Blatant Image and Sinister Wisdom. In 1981, Cottrell received a BA in film studies from San Francisco State University. She was director and camera for Sweet Dreams, starring Pat Califia (National Sex Forum, 1980), and from 1985 to the early 90s, a cinematographer for Fatale Video, the first lesbian-created erotic movie company. She photographed her lovers and friends and documented queer and kink cultures for decades with her first camera, a 35 mm Nikkormat.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Personal papers and photographic archives. Also, erotic and sex education videos of interest to lesbians and others by S.I.R. video production company, run by Shar Rednour and Jackie Strano, circa late 1980s, early 1990s. Shar and Jackie collaborated with Honey Lee to photograph and visualize projects. Honey Lee took photos of Shar for her book cover for The Femme's Ultimate Guide to the Universe. Photographs, event publicity, and files. Includes photos of Phyllis Christopher, friend and staff photographer for the periodical On Our Backs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cottrell, Honey Lee, 1946-2015; Bright, Susie, 1958-; Califia, Patrick, 1954-; Corinne, Tee, 1943-2006; Hollibaugh, Amber L., 1946-; Kinney, Nan.; Rubin, Gayle.; Sundahl, Deborah.
Titles:
On our backs.
Subjects:
Butch and femme (Lesbian culture).; Erotica.; Feminism.; Lesbians -- Pictorial works.; Photography, Erotic.; Photography of women.; Pornographic films.; Pornography.; Sex instruction.; Sex oriented businesses.; Women -- Sexual behavior.; Women-owned business enterprises.; Erotica.; Feminism.; Pornographic films.; Pornography.; Sex instruction.; Sex-oriented businesses.; Women-owned business enterprises.; Women -- Sexual behavior.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Digital scans of some photographs are also available through the digital portal.
NOTES
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Photographs
Series Ia. Erotic Portraits
Series Ib. On Our Backs photographs
Series Ic. Personal Photographs
Series Id. General Photographs
Series Ie. Famous Lesbians
Series If. Slides
Series II. Paper Documents
Series III. Publications
Series IV. Interviews
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Photographs
  - Series Ia. Erotic Portraits
    - Cottrell's handwritten list of Erotic Portraits, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Erotic Portraits: Gayle Rubin and Pat Califia, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Erotic Portraits: Amber Hollibaugh, Jim Garver of the National Sex Forum, time of the Barnard Conference on Sexuality, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Erotic Portraits: Pat Avenues (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Erotic Portraits: Jeff and Mark (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Erotic Portraits: Rhonda (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Erotic Portraits: Judith Chicago (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Carla and Mark Chester, Mythic Postcard Series, January, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Nancy and John, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Includes negatives.
    - Susie and Steven (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Morgan and Beth, February, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Lee Rae (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Victor (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Angela and Lewanda (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Lady Chatterly (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - On Our Backs photographs
    - Chris and Susie Porn Picnic (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Studio Test: Erica, Jill, Honey (playing hockey), Rhonda and Friends (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - TS [transsexual]: Jamie and Lauren [later Loren Rex Cameron] at Bessie Street, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      The first two transmen who agreed/asked to be photographed and interviewed for OOB. Includes "Rites of Passage" Newsletter, Volume 1 Number 1.
    - Jacqueline Livingston exhibit prints (Map-case 1)
    - Subway Pictorial Final prints extras for working script (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Stripper Jessica and Elexis, Rachael and Elexis (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Contains prints and contact sheets from the photo shoot that produced the widely published photograph of Rachael Williams and Elexis, "Coastside Train."
    - Dildo ad prints and contacts (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Food Comic (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Leather Fashion Pic Prints (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Dossie and Babs in the Woods contacts and prints (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Boy Porn (Box 2, Folder 24)
      First OOB photo showing nude male.
    - Safe Sex (Box 2, Folder 25)
      For feature about making safe sex sexy and understandable.
    - Gay Games - San Francisco, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Donna and Barbara (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Cassy and Lauri proofs and prints, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Rolo (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Susie, Debi, Staff promo prints, Lulu Belliveau, and movie Theatershot (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Sarah Davis (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Nina and Bobby, January, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Nina and Bobby- The Hunt layouts, letter about the story (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Personal photographs
    - Portfolio of personal photographs, Undated (Box 1)
      Given to Curator Brenda Marston near the time of her death.
      Includes photo of Honey Lee playing the harmonica as a child; self-portraits, other photographs and collages by Honey Lee Cottrell; photographs by Tee Corinne; letterhead for Duanne and Patricia in Leslie, Michigan; photographs of Gayle Rubin, Pat Califia, Amber Hollibaugh, Tee Corinne, and unlabelled photographs.
    - Large black and white prints of Honey Lee's photographs (Box 8)
    - List of personal photographs (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Old insert shots, including little Honey and Family and Paris (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Holiday cards and portraits (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Michael Rosen and Gen Portraits of H and S (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Moving Out, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Spinellis and Haircut (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Spinelli's was a coffee shop on 24th Street
    - Memorial Day Barbeque (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Susie Birth photos, June, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Includes negatives. UCSF Hospital
    - Perfect Apple (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Honey with Calla Lilly (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Taken by Susie
    - Susie and New House (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Assorted Susie (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Assorted Honey (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Family, with Aretha's birth announcement and newspaper clippings (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Erotic Portraiture, Amber and Honey (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Amber and Honey went to Baja California on vacation
    - Piercing (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Raelynn Gallina died of cancer about a year before Honey, and was the first serious lesbian piercer
    - Gerald and Honey Wedding prints (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Gerald was a Chinese businessman Honey Lee married as a green card favor
    - Honey Porn (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Three binders of some of Honey Lee's favorite photographs, including cards and childhood photographs (Box 6)
    - Two binders and an album of some of Honey Lee's favorite photographs (Box 5)
    - Large prints of some of Honey Lee's favorite photographs (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
      Including Paris, London, Samois, Tee, Steven, Cinderdyke, Luce and Susan, Scorpio, Gay Day, March on Wash, Born Butch, old lesbian historical photos, history project parade.
    - Presentation portfolio of large prints (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Portrait of Gayle Rubin, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous travel photographs, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous negatives and contacts (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
      Includes Triple Play San Ramon, Susie, Aretha, Lisa Palac, Pat and Gayle, Jane and Sally, and more
    - Miscellaneous prints (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
      Closeups of flowers, travel photographs.
    - Pictures of a farm and of people, with hand drawings of a barn and the layout of Decatur, Michigan. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 19 black and white photos by Honey Lee Cottrell and a Tee Corinne image possibly printed by Cottrell, 1977-03, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Includes California whitewater rafting trips organized by Seeley, Maxine Feldman
    - 2 images from Seeley and Cottrell's trip to Europe and 4 color photographs by Marsha Seeley of Cottrell and Maxine Feldman, San Francisco, 1977-03, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Series Id. General Photographs
    In Honey Lee Cottrell's original order, many annotated or labelled by Susie Bright.
    - SIR, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Includes SIR production agreements
    - SIR photos and PR, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Shar Rednour, Jackie Strano photos and PR. 1 Photo by "P. Christopher 93"
    - Susie Bright book cover photo shoot, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Includes some images from Tee Corinne shoot
    - TEE memorial photo, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Includes newspaper
    - Erica Marcus, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Donna McBride, Barbara Grier, and Calla Lily, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Foxy Francias and Vixens, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Sally Binford, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Honey Lee portrait as a toddler with parents, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Susie, Cynthia Slater image used in On Our Backs, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Honey Lee calendar, family, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Mixed/small album prints, undated (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
      Includes pressed butterfly wings
    - Negative/Contact Sheets, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Photoshop, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Various photographs, Undated, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      Includes notes and San Francisco Lesbian and Gay History Project photos
    - Mixed single album sex portraits, circa 1970s-2005 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Lesbian and Gay History Project, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Various photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Real Dykes, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Theory OOB Pictorials, 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      Honey Lee's description of her collage work
    - Contact sheets Tee, Amber, and HLC Nude duo, Sinister Wisdom Poster, Flyers, Dick Show, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
      Dick Show flyers, and Susie giving birth
    - Conference Omaha Nebraska, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Scorpio Sabi, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Webster St., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Europe Trip, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Photographs by Tee Corinne, undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Women in the national sex forum, undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Melinda Gebi, Mid-1990s (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Melinda and Honey Lee, undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Honey Lee in Paris, undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Canyon Sam, undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Women kissing, published in OOB, undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Sepia collage prints and others with HLC, undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Erotic portraits and Robin Flower, mid-1980s (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Miss Leather Contest prints and negatives, 1981, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Sex Write, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Various, undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Sally and Jan, Sally and Jeremy, undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Lily Pond, undated (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Mime make-up, a lover, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Fillmore St. Couple, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Cynthia Slater, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Gay man in garden erotic portrait, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Fiji, when HLC was working on ship, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - A lover?, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Leather man portrait, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - "Shy" gay man erotic portrait, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Lesbian couple, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Sex ed book commission, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Cowboy and Chicken, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Gay couple, private erotic portrait, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Amber at brick hut, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Susan Stern, Spain, Lava Sundahl, pregnant SB, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - HLC Lover, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Jealousy collage, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - River raft dyke trip, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Play at gay theater st., undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Amber/Tee, HLC Collage, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Portrait of unknown subject, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Lee Ray, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Unknown portraits, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Stefan, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - HLC and Susie Bright posing for Michael Rosen, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Romantic photos of Susie by HLC, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - OOB stills, test prints, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Cleo Dubois, "Carla", Mark Chester, Susie Bright, at 25A Bessie, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - BC Cliver, Kitty Tsui, gay friends for OOB, Honey's famous dyke series, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Caitlin/Wayman, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Women in Print contact sheets and negatives, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Tee ovular, Oregon, undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Stephen erotic portraits, circa 1980 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Cinderdyke, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      Unpublished Bessie St. SB and HLC breakup photos.
    - Stormy Leather prints and catalogue, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Lesbian couple, erotic portrait customers, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Jen DiGioa, Aretha at Folsum St. Fair, circa 1993 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - C-5 infant daycare, undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Various famous dykes portraits, undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - The Dyke Bike Repair Book, undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Gay Parade, Washington DC, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Nan Butch Portfolio, undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Rudy Minyard playing pool, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Birdie, undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Jenni Olsen, Frameline years, undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Triple Play at Amazon Motel, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Valerie Taylor at Donna McBride and Barbara Grier house, undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Pat Bond and Pat's WWII photographs, undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - LBGH Project marches in SF Parade, undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
      Amber, Eric, Molly, Birdie, Allan B
    - Contact sheets for Rachael calendar, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - "Just Sex" by Arms Akimbo, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
      Appeared on SF new stands one night
    - Pretty Renee on Manchester St., undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Self portrait, Tee era, undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Webster St. apartment dykes, the French visitors, Pat Califia, Cynthia Slater, Tee Corinne, HLC, undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Sarah Davis featured in Berube's "Coming Home", undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Shey Castro cop, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Contact sheets, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
      From orange box.
    - Contact sheets, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
      From green box.
    - Presentation book of prints, articles, and fliers, 1970s-1990s (Box 11)
    - Sketch book, 1969-1971 (Box 11)
    - Portfolio of prints, magazines, art, and ephemera, undated (Box 11)
    - Photo and negative strips, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Subseries Ie. Famous Lesbians
    Organized and annotated by Susie Bright, many of these belong to a series that Honey Lee called Famous Lesbians.
    - Susie Bright and Christian Mann, 1986 or 1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Buck in Sex Forum days when Tee Corinne, Pat Califia (Hartman), Cynthia Slater, and HLC were friends (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Also Barbara Grier, Donna McBride
    - The Memorial at Castro Street and 18th street (Hibernia Beach), undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
      "Where gay men paid a huge tribute to Lucille Ball on occasion of her death. One of the last grand "old gay" gestures in the Castro."
    - Tee Corinne photo to Honey Lee, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Linda Farin "The Foosh", undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
      "From Austin, she came to SF to be a film-maker. The only one of HL's Famous dykes who didn't become famous."
    - Tee's portrait of Honey Lee, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Stormy Leather, Deb and Koko, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Tee, Ovular, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Cinderdyke, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Famous Dykes, autographed, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Ruby Minyara, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Jenny Olsen, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Triple Play, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Just Sex, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Jen di Gioa and Aretha, Folsum St. Fair, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Scorpio, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Family, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
      Includes rubbing of family plaque
    - Slides: Susie Promo Chromes, Summer '99 and others, 1999, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Greta Schiller, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Jenni Olsen, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Honey Lee Self portrait, SB Snapped, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Debi AKA Fanny Fatale, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Gayle Rubin, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Birdie Yusbu, Golden Gate Park, San Francisco, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      Roberta “Birdie” Yusba, an important founding member of the SF Gay and Lesbian History Project who researched and created an educational slideshow about lesbian-themed pulp novels
    - Nan Kenney in front of St. Peter's in North Beach, San Francisco, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      Photograph taken the same year Kinney played the cashier in Monika Treut’s movie Die Jungfrauen Maschine (Virgin Machine).
    - Rachael Williams, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      Rachael Williams, a Black dyke who in 1981 became the first Ms. Leather and the first Black person to hold the equivalent of a national title.
    - Christian and Susie, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Pat Califia, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Subseries If. Slides
    - Classic Iconic slides, including Bulldagger center fold, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - London, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Amber/Honey, Bernal Hill, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
    - Lee Rae, undated (Box 12)
    - Marsha Ovular, Birth Ritual, undated (Box 12)
    - Joice and Ted, Mom and Dad, undated (Box 12)
    - Pat before s/m, s/m dance/Amber, undated (Box 12)
    - Amber, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Copenhaven, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Family, Mom and Dad, visits home, undated (Box 12)
    - Cynthia and horse (2 boxes), undated (Box 12)
    - Melinda, undated (Box 12)
    - Framed large color photos, undated (Box 12)
    - Susie and Shirley Muldowney, undated (Box 12)
    - Knife Paper Scissors (3 boxes), undated (Box 12)
    - Westley, undated (Box 12)
    - Erotic portraiture, female, undated (Box 12)
    - Framed work, undated (Box 12)
    - Rene Vivien, Natatie Barney, Paris, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Honey Lee, undated (Box 12)
    - Honey Lee self-portrait, portraits of Susie, undated (Box 12)
- Series II. Paper Documents
  - Countervision and On Our Backs vision statements, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    An advertising flyer for On Our Backs with information about Countervision on the reverse.
  - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Including miscellaneous photographs, letters from family, graduation material, and a small password book
  - Portrait drawing by Melinda (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Poster for "The Vulvart Show", April 23, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Altered poster of the Nutcracker, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Nothing But the Girl, thoughts on Lesbian photography, with photograph (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Magazine covers with Shar Rednour, Jackie Strano (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - On Our Backs 5th Anniversary, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Testing the Limits, 1960s-1970s, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    Black and white scans of her personal scrapbooks
  - Tony and Ruby Review, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Bulldagger Self-portrait, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Nothing But The Girl, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    Response to meeting with Susie.
  - Women in Print Conference 1977, sent to Barbara Grier 1989, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Ferd Eggan, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Arlene Stein interview with HLC about her life, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - N.A.M.E. Gallery Show, December 7, 1990; 1993 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Japanese anime lecture, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Tee Corinne letters, 1970s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Copies of Duane Cottrell historic documents, HLC's copy, undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Duane stationary, undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - "A Cartoon Story" by P. Cottrell, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - HLC short stories, 1973, 2006, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Family scrapbook, undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
    Loose papers, clippings, correspondence, and photos.
  - Cottrell genealogy, January, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Sherri-Sherri letter to HLC, March 7, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Concepts on four OOB pictorials, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Scorpio products correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Series III. Publications
  - Vasta catalogues, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Albatross, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Sex Issue, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Eldos, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Facilitator's Guide to Eroticizing Sex, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Harley Women, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Yellow Silk, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Inside, No. 2 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Art in Jeopardy: an Exhibition Curated by Jeannie Kamins, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - The Sexuality Library (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - National Lesbian and Gay Writers Conference: Outwrite, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - The Best of Wimmen's Comix, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Body Play, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sexual Portraits and Private Acts from the Warzone Mark Chester (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sexual Portraits Mark Rosen, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Frisko, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Drummer, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Cupido, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Quim, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Amour Fou: Photography and Surrealism, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Xenogenesis calendar, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Lesbian Lust number 2 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Word City Works, Chicago Council on Fine Arts Artists in Residence Program, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Diary of a Conference: on Sexuality, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Venus Infers, volume 1 number 4 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Heirs, with note to Honey Lee from Melinda, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Libido, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Stormy Leather (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Cunt Coloring Book, drawings by Tee Corinne (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Two copies, one with signatures and notes
  - On Our Backs, January-June, November 1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - On Our Backs, January-October, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - On Our Backs, January 1992, September 1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - On Our Backs calendar, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Series IV. Interviews
  - Interview of Honey Lee Cottrell by Brenda Marston, September 6, 2015